(Bernadette:)when you don't get
your allowance.
(Howard:)It's not an allowance.
It's a stipend!
(Howard:)And we said we weren't gonna
call it an allowance
(Howard:)in front of my friends.
(door slams)
(Leonard:)I usually don't like
lemon bars,
but th-these are really good.
(Raj:)So, as Hannah
Montana, Miley
(Raj:)was a world-famous pop star.
(Raj:)But then she would take off
her wig and go to school
(Leonard:)like a
normal girl.
(Raj:)Which, I don't have to tell you,
(Raj:)at that age,
is its own headache.
(Sheldon:)That's preposterous.
(Sheldon:)How would she go unrecognized
just by wearing a wig?
(Raj:)But you're okay with Superman
concealing his identity
(Raj:)with a pair of glasses?
(Sheldon:)He doesn't just put on a pair
of glasses.
(Sheldon:)He combs back his curlicue
(Sheldon:)and affects
a mild-mannered personality.
AMY:
You guys doing
okay down there?
(Sheldon:)I told you to use
the walkie-talkie!
(Amy(shouting):)You guys doing okay down there?
(Sheldon:)Please keep this channel clear
for emergencies. Thank you.